git lfs ls-files [<ref>]
git lfs ls-files <ref> <ref>

Display paths of Git LFS files that are found in the tree at the given
reference. If no reference is given, scan the currently checked-out
branch. If two references are given, the LFS files that are modified
between the two references are shown; deletions are not listed.

An asterisk (*) after the OID indicates a full object, a minus (-)
indicates an LFS pointer.

Options:

-l:
--long:
   Show the entire 64 character OID, instead of just first 10.
-s:
--size:
   Show the size of the LFS object between parenthesis at the end of a line.
-d:
--debug:
   Show as much information as possible about a LFS file. This is intended for
   manual inspection; the exact format may change at any time.
-a:
--all:
   Inspects the full history of the repository, not the current HEAD (or other
   provided reference). This will include previous versions of LFS objects that
   are no longer found in the current tree.
--deleted:
  Shows the full history of the given reference, including objects that have
  been deleted.
-I <paths>:
--include=<paths>:
   Include paths matching only these patterns; see "Fetch settings".
-X <paths>:
--exclude=<paths>:
   Exclude paths matching any of these patterns; see "Fetch settings".
-n:
--name-only:
   Show only the lfs tracked file names.
